We're happy to announce increased defense spending on the
"North American aerospace defense command infrastructure " by another "four billion dollars".
Well, that's good news.
Finally, NORAD's radar warning system will get some upgrades.
Yeah, with all those hypersonic missiles everyone's been making, it's about heck in time.
Maybe Canada will finally start making its NATO military spending agreements.
Yeah......, but do you have a feel like there's....... something a bit... off about him?
I don't know what you're talking about...I'm gonna go shoot beer bottles, while drinking guns... I mean drinking beers.
okay guys,,, you know the plan.
just think of it basically like wild rain back in the day.
if we each stick to our roles ,he won't know what hit him. Oh...it's him...We've been made.
Oh...it's him...We've been made.
It's the god damn radar upgrade.
This man sees everything coming now.
I am not soaring anymore...