hi and welcome to the channel my name is haigo and today we wanna do a little Halloween decoration, not the usual pumpkin carving and ghost gluing stuff.
we want to colorize Flames for fire pits and fireplaces. let's go!!!
all right what do we need? we need some wax for sure. we have to melt it in a minute. I will do that.
we need some pine cones
ummm... I take that as a base because I like how they look. if they burn they're looking kind of cool in the fireplace.
that's the reason I take this. you will find them all over the place no problems with that.
some twine doesn't matter what kind of.
and then we need why we turn the Flames into different colors. it's because we're burning salts different kind of salts .for example, this would be Alum and we'll turn the flame green and so on. so I put in the description some salts that and there is effective colors if they burn.
but I like this pre-mixed thing because if these are in the fire then they will change the color of the Flames randomly.
so this is pretty cool I like this more than a unique color or a single color but it's a matter of taste you can do both .yeah I will just quickly melt this
and by the way I want to show you three easy methods for coloring the Flames
all we need molten wax you can give the salt directly into the Flames but with the wax it is easier to handle
and you add some fuel to the fire so that you have a better effect at the end but I get ahead of myself
and here I melt the wax in hot water that takes a little while and if all the wax is liquid I add the fire powder so the basically the salts to the molten wax I think for this amount of wax 8 to 10 teaspoons is pretty okay
all right for our third method now we need the wax to be nearly cold so the putty kind of texture
so that you can easily form little balls out of the wax
my camera really is not a bad piece of equipment at all but filming different colored Flames during night it pushes my camera to its limits.I try to collect some nice shots for you
and I made some shots in my fireplace during daytime just to give you an impression how the Flames look like
my advice would be do not bring the wax or the salt into burning fire you more put it into the Amber and then you have nice Flames
the wax give the fuel so you have nice Flames nice colored Flames that would be a good surprise for guests or for kids.
or it's just for you enjoying nice colored Flames. I hope you liked that video and I hope you guys see you next time around happy boohoo